Hello everyone, today I’ll show you how to use
the Medical Encyclopaedia by Javi and Álvaro,
a website for quickly and easily finding
medical terms.
When you enter, you’ll see a search bar at the
top and, just below, buttons with letters of the
alphabet. These allow you to easily navigate
based on the initial letter of the condition you’re looking for.
To find a condition, click on the letter that
its name starts with, like “A”
for “allergies” or “anxiety” or “D” for
“diabetes.” This will take you to an index
of conditions beginning with that letter.
Within the index, select the specific condition
you’re looking for. You’ll find a brief, direct
explanation, and in some cases, charts or diagrams
that help you understand the term quickly.
You can return to the main menu or the
list of letters to continue exploring
additional terms.
And that’s it! Now you know how to use
the Medical Encyclopaedia by Javi and Álvaro
to consult medical terms quickly
and effectively. Thanks for watching!